http://www.knowledgenetwork.ca/terms-privacy

Skip to main content
Privacy
Knowledge Network Corporation is committed to the protection of the personal information of its donors, viewers, employees, directors, volunteers, clients and other stakeholders. As a public body, Knowledge Network Corporation is subject to British Columbia’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (“FIPPA”).
FIPPA sets out the requirements under which Knowledge may collect, use and disclose personal information. We collect personal information that relates directly to and is necessary for the administration of our programs and activities as permitted in Section 26(c), (d) and (e) of FIPPA.
“Personal information” is any recorded information about an identifiable individual. Personal information includes, but is not limit to, an individual’s name, address, birth date, e-mail address, phone number, country, persistent identifiers including an individual’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, customer number held in a cookie, a processor or device serial number, or a unique device identifier that can be used to recognize an individual over time and across different websites or online services.
In order to provide you with an excellent customer service experience, when you contact Knowledge Network, we may collect any of the foregoing personal information. This enables us to (a) respond to your enquiries, (b) process your donations, (c) notify you about our programs, events and fundraising initiatives, (d) better understand general user trends at an aggregate level, and (e) improve the Web Services (as defined below) and website maintenance. Personal information will only be used for the intent that it was collected – to effectively deliver Knowledge Network services and programs including our fundraising program.
Employees will only access your personal information in order to fulfill their job duties and serve you. We will not sell, rent or trade your personal information. Vendors contracted to support Knowledge Network’s fundraising program are committed to protecting the personal information entrusted to them.
At any time, you may contact us to correct any personal information about you that we may have in our records.
We will update the information promptly.
Contact Information
If you have questions or concerns relating to the treatment of personal information, they can be directed Knowledge Network Privacy Officer:
By phone: 604-431-3222 or Toll Free 1-877-456-6988
By email: privacy@knowledge.ca
By Mail:
Privacy Officer
Knowledge Network Corporation
4355 Mathissi Place
Burnaby, BC
V5G 4S8
Further information on privacy and your rights in regard to your personal information may be found on the website of the Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner (OIPC).
Privacy – Web Services
Jump to Terms of Use here
Knowledge Network Corporation has developed its digital services, including various Apps, the Knowledge.ca website and the Knowledgekids.ca website (each a “Web Service”, collectively the “Web Services”), as electronic resources with information about our organization and its programs, and as fun and entertaining streaming services for our viewing audience.
We are committed to providing our visitors with Web Services that respect their privacy. We encourage and support the efforts of parents and legal guardians of children to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to caution them against providing personal information to any website or App without their permission.
Information Collected Through Web Services
When you use our Web Services, you may be subject to the collection of a limited amount of information essential for the operation and security of our Web Services. Some of this information (for example, your browser type) does not identify who you are, while other information, such as your Internet domain name or IP address, may identify you. To the extent Internet domain names or IP addresses may identify you, and are necessary to the use of our Web Services, your continued use of our Web Services indicates your receipt of this notice of our use and collection of that information to the extent necessary for our provision of the Web Services to you or as otherwise set out in this policy.
Personal information voluntarily provided by you via our Web Services will be used for the purpose for which it was provided (for example, to enter a contest, participate in an online forum, make a donation, send an inquiry, or send an email address to receive automatic information about upcoming programming) or to which you otherwise consent, will be kept strictly confidential, and is not disclosed to anyone inside Knowledge except the personnel who need the information to complete your request
Such information may also be used for internal analysis for management purposes, solely to the extent authorized under the FIPPA.
Your Registration Information: Certain services offered through our Web Services may require you to register with us. Registration at our Web Services requires that you provide your first and last name, email address and postal code as well as select a secure password. Internet Protocol (IP) addresses are also collected and linked to your registration information.
We collect this information for statistical purposes and for evaluating our website to make it more useful to visitors. Our Web Services records the IP addresses of computers that contact our web site. We use these addresses to generate geographic-related statistics, and to help administer the Web Services, in general. We make no attempt to link addresses with the identities of individuals visiting our site and such information is kept secure and confidential. We may use your other personal information collected through our registration form to contact you for fundraising purposes in order to provide you with opportunities to support our services and programming.
Some features of our Web Services require information about your location in order to operate, as some of the content in our Web Services is only available in B.C. or Canada. When you access our Web Services from a personal computer, general location information for the personal computer is accessed by our systems to determine availability of service.
In some instances, we may use outside parties to process donations, administer contests, promotions and other online activities on our behalf. This may involve the collection of personal information. In such cases, we ensure that the manner in which any outside party collects, uses and retains personal information conforms to our privacy policies and is in strict compliance with FIPPA.
We may disclose personal information to affiliates and outside suppliers or contractors from whom we obtain services for the purposes of supplying those services, provided such disclosures are limited to the individuals providing those services and then only to the extent required to facilitate the provision of those services. Knowledge does not sell, license, rent, market, disclose, barter or distribute any personal information obtained from our Web Services other than as disclosed in this statement.
Mobile Apps
This section sets out additional information about how your personal information is collected and used when you use our Apps.
Our Apps for children (“Kids Apps”) do not require registration. Kids Apps may require a user name for use of games but this is used solely for purposes of operation of the game and we make no attempt to link usage information with the identity of individuals using our Apps.
Some features of our mobile Apps for adults may require registration in order to operate. When you register in our Apps you are required to provide your first and last name, email address and postal code, as well as select a secure password. We use your email address collected through registration in our Apps to contact you for fundraising purposes in order to provide you with opportunities to support our services and programming.
Our Apps collect information regarding your use of the App. Some features of our Apps require information about your location in order to operate as some of the content in our Apps is only available in B.C. or in Canada.
When you access our Web Services from an app, general location information for the app is accessed by our systems to determine availability of service.
Information Automatically Collected
We maintain server logs, web logs, and other industry-standard technologies which automatically collect certain information regarding users of our Web Services, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, the IP address of your Internet Service Provider, and the date and time you access our Web Services. This information is used for our Web Services and system administration purposes.
We may review server logs for security purposes, for example to detect intrusions into our network. The possibility exists that server log data, which contains visitors’ IP addresses, could in instances of criminal or other malfeasance, or where necessary to protect the security and integrity of our Web Services, be used to trace and identify individuals and be shared with appropriate investigative bodies and others as permitted by law.
Cookies and Anonymous Identifiers
Our Web Services use “cookies” and/or other industry-standard technologies that install(s) information on a user’s computer to track how our visitors use the Web Services and to permit the Web Services to recognize future visits using that computer. You may choose to decline cookies, if your browser permits, by modifying the Preferences section of your Internet browser software, but doing so may affect your use of our Web Services and your ability to access certain features of our Web Services.
We have implemented web analytics tools including Google Analytics to help us gain insights on how our Web Services are used. These third-party services use various technologies, including cookies and other anonymous identifiers, to collect and store information about your use of our Web Services and third- party sites. Learn more about how Google collects and uses this data.
Our Web Services may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to examine each site's privacy policy and make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability and correctness of material and information found.
We will Protect You when You are on our Web Services
Our Web Services may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to examine each site's privacy policy and make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability and correctness of material and information found.
Security
Knowledge uses a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. All user contact information is contained behind secured networks and is accessible only by a limited number of trusted employees and/or contractors who have special access rights to production systems. Passwords are encrypted in Knowledge’s secure database, which is also located behind secured networks. All sensitive/credit card information is transported and processed in accordance with credit card industry security standards.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
This statement is in effect as of August 19, 2020.
Terms of Use – Web Services
Jump to Privacy here
Knowledge Network Corporation (“Knowledge”) provides its digital services, including various Apps, the knowledge.ca website and the knowledgekids.ca website (each a “Web Service”, collectively the “Web Services”), as electronic resources with information about our organization and its programs, and as fun and entertaining services for our viewing audience. Access to and use of the Web Services is provided subject to these Terms of Use.
Effective Date: September 28, 2015
Your Acceptance of These Terms and Conditions
These Terms of Use represent an agreement between you and Knowledge. Your use of any portion of the Web Services constitutes your agreement to the terms and conditions set out below. If you do not accept the terms and conditions stated here, do not use the Web Services.
Knowledge reserves the right to change the terms and conditions under which the Web Services are offered at any time, without notice. These Terms of Use may be subject to change, addition or deletion at any time. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these Terms of Use. By using the Web Services you are agreeing to be bound by the then-current version of these Terms of Use.
Use of Web Services by Children
Our Web Services include safe and educational children’s content that family members of all ages can enjoy. However not all content may be appropriate for children, and parents and guardians are advised to exercise supervision over their children’s use of our Web Services. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, do not let your child use the Web Services.
All Web Services that require registration are restricted to persons who are 19 years of age or older. If you are not yet 19 years old do not register on our Web Services.
All Communications Services are restricted to persons who are 15 years of age or older. If you are not yet 15 years old do not use the Communications Services. Persons who are at least 15 but not yet 19 years of age require parental consent to use our Communication Services.
Our Trademarks
KNOWLEDGE NETWORK, KNOWLEDGE:, K: KIDS, KNOWLEDGE: KIDS, K:, and KNOWLEDGE: PARTNERS are trademarks and official marks owned by Knowledge Network Corporation. Other trademarks, trade names, logos and designs reference or appearing in the Web Services are proprietary to Knowledge Network Corporation or other entities. Any use of the trade names, trademarks, service marks and logos displayed in the Web Services (collectively “Marks”) is strictly prohibited. Nothing appearing in the Web Services or elsewhere should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any licence or right to use any Marks.
Our Ownership of the Web Services and its Content
All content published on or otherwise accessible through the Web Services (“Content”) (including, without limitation, the texts, graphics articles, photographs, images, illustrations, audio recordings, videos, software, etc.) is protected by copyright and belong to Knowledge or third parties acting as content providers. Unauthorized use of any Content may violate copyright, trade-mark and other laws. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Restrictions on Use
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the Content on the Web Services for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. You may not use the Web Services for any other purpose or in any other way. This is a grant of a licence, not a transfer of title, and under this licence you may not:
copy, reproduce, modify or create derivative works from the Content except as specifically provided above or except as expressly authorized in the Web Services;
use the Content for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (whether commercial or non-commercial);
upload, post, transmit, index, catalogue, mirror, publish or distribute the Content in any way, in whole or in part;
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained in the Web Services; or
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the Content.
No licence is given for republication, distribution, performance, display, translation, retransmission, broadcast, sublicense, or any use other than non-commercial personal use. You must access all Content manually by request and not programmably by machine automated means. You may not use any Content for any unlawful purpose.
You may not copy or adapt the HTML that Knowledge creates to generate its pages. It is also protected by Knowledge’s copyright.
All Content and services contained or provided in the Web Services including, without limitation, all Communication Services (as hereinafter defined), are offered for your personal use for non-commercial purposes. It is prohibited to use anything contained in the Web Services for commercial or advertising purposes.
This license will automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Knowledge at any time. On terminating your viewing of these materials or the termination of this license, you must destroy all Content obtained from the Web Services and all copies thereof, whether made under the terms of these Terms of Use or otherwise.
Knowledge Network Mobile Applications
This section sets out additional terms and conditions applying to your use of Knowledge Network Apps for mobile devices (each an “App”, collectively “Apps”). Apps are available for download at third party app stores. When you download an App Knowledge grants you a non-exclusive, revocable licence to install and use the App and App Content on your mobile device, subject to your compliance with these Terms of Use including the additional terms and conditions in this section. Apps are licensed under the terms and conditions of these Terms of Use, not sold to you.
Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, no licence to use, copy, distribute, republish, transmit or otherwise exploit the App or any Content contained in the App is given to you, and all intellectual property rights in and to the App and the Content are expressly reserved to Knowledge or its licensors, as applicable. You may not attempt, or authorize, encourage, or support others’ attempts to circumvent, reverse engineer, decrypt, break or otherwise alter or interfere with the App. You acknowledge and agree that the App is for your personal use only. You acknowledge and agree that except as herein expressly permitted, you may not copy, modify, distribute, sell, re-sell, or exploit for any commercial purposes any portion of the App. You agree to be fully liable for any unauthorized access to or use of the App.
These Terms and Conditions will govern any updates or upgrades provided by Knowledge that replace and/or supplement the original App, unless such update or upgrade is accompanied by a separate licence in which case the terms of that licence will govern.
Knowledge reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify, edit, delete, suspend or discontinue, temporarily or permanently any App (or any portion thereof) and/or the information materials, products and/or services available through the App (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that Knowledge will not be liable to you or any third party for any such modification, editing, deletion, suspension or discontinuance of any App. Knowledge also reserves the right to deny, revoke or disable your access to the App, or any part thereof, and terminate your rights thereunder, at any time in its sole discretion, with or without cause and with or without notice to you.
Your rights under this licence will terminate automatically without notice from Knowledge if you fail to comply with any terms of these Terms of Use. Upon termination of the licence, you shall cease all use of the App, and destroy all copies, full or partial of the App.
It is your responsibility to accept any updates to the app to ensure that you are working with the most current version. Notwithstanding the foregoing, knowledge assumes no liability to update or keep current the information and content provided in the app.
Our Apps for children (“Kids Apps”) require that a parent or legal guardian consent to use by children under the age of 15. Kids Apps do not require registration for use, but may employ a parental gate or other method to assist parents in supervising their children’s use of our Kids Apps. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use do not let your child use our Kids Apps.
Consent to Use of Data
You agree that Knowledge may collect and use technical data and related information, including but limited to technical information about your device, system and application software, and peripherals, that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support or any other services to you (if any) related to the App. Knowledge may use this information, as long as it is in a form that does not personally identify you, to improve its products or to provide services or technologies to you.
Notice of Disclaimer
The Web Services provide information, resources and links about Knowledge services and about a variety of topics which may be of interest to you. They are provided for information only and should not be interpreted as a recommendation for a specific course of action and should not be relied on for personal, medical, legal or financial decisions. Users are cautioned not to act on any information provided without seeking advice specific to their circumstances from a qualified professional.
The content on the Web Services is provided “as is”, “as available” and without warranties or conditions of any kind either express or implied. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Knowledge expressly disclaims all warranties and conditions, express or implied, including but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, and warranties of non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Knowledge makes no representations or warranties regarding the use, accuracy, completeness, timeliness, applicability, performance, security, safety from any software virus or other harmful component, availability or reliability of the Web Services or any sites linked to the Web Services, or the results from the use of the Web Services or any sites linked to by the Web Services, or otherwise respecting, the content on the Web Services or any sites linked to the Web Services. Knowledge does not warrant that the function of the Web Services or its contents will be uninterrupted or error free. Knowledge will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of, or in connection with your use of, or reliance on, any content on the Web Services or any third party site. Your use of the Web Services is at your own risk.
Contests
Knowledge may, from time to time, run contests through the Web Services, alone or jointly with third party sponsors. All such contests will be governed by their respective contest rules. Prior to entering into a contest, you should read, understand and agree to the terms and conditions set out in the applicable contest rules.
Links to Third Party Sites
The Web Services may contain, and other users or third parties may provide, information on or links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. These sites and resources are not controlled by Knowledge, and the mere existence of the link on the Web Services does not imply an endorsement or sponsorship by Knowledge. External Web sites and resources are not subject to these Terms of Use or the Knowledge Web Services or Privacy Statements and may be subject to other terms and conditions or policies posted therein. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Web Services and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each other website you visit.
Because Knowledge has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that Knowledge is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites or resources or the privacy policies and practices at any such sites. You further acknowledge and agree that Knowledge shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any goods or services available on or through any external site or resource. Your use of external sites or resources is at your own risk. You expressly release Knowledge from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party website.
No Linking, Framing, Mirroring, Scraping or Data Mining
Links to the Web Services without the express permission of Knowledge are strictly prohibited. To request permission to link to any Web Service, please contact Knowledge (mail to: info@knowledge.ca). The framing, mirroring, scraping or data mining of the Web Services or any Content in any form and by any method is strictly prohibited.
No Endorsement
Description of, or reference to, third party companies, products or publications in the Web Services is for informational purposes only and constitutes neither an endorsement or recommendation.
No Unlawful or Prohibited Use
As a condition of your use of the Web Services, you warrant to Knowledge that you will not use the Web Services for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use. You agree not to disturb the normal operation of the Web Services, and not to infringe the integrity of the Web Services by hacking, altering the information contained in the Web Services or otherwise. You may not use the Web Services in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Web Services or interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the Web Services. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the Web Services.
Registration and Security
Certain of the services offered in the Web Services may require you to register with us. Some features of our Apps for adult users may require registration to operate. When you register with any Web Service, you must select a password and provide your email address. You must not (i) choose or use someone’s password or email address with the intention of pretending to be that person; (ii) use a password or email address in which someone else has rights, without that person’s authorization; or (iii) use a password that Knowledge, at its sole discretion, considers offensive.
You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. You should notify Knowledge as soon as possible at info@knowledge.ca or 604.431.3222 of any known or suspected use of your account, or of any known or suspected breach of security.
You are responsible for any use of your accounts on the Web Services. Knowledge cannot be held liable for the unauthorized use of your account or for any loss or damage arising in particular from the non-compliance with the security measures mentioned in this section.
Use of Communication Services
The Web Services may contain bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal web pages, calendars, user content platforms, and/or message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with the public at large or with a group (individually a “Communication Service”, collectively “Communication Services”). When using the Communication Services, you will be subject to any posted code of conduct, terms or guidelines applicable to such services. Any posted code of conduct, terms or guidelines are hereby incorporated by reference into these Terms of Use.
You must be an individual of 15 years of age or older to use any Communication Service. If you are not yet 15 years old, do not use the Communication Services.
If you are at least 15 but not yet 19 years of age: Please have your parents or legal guardian review these Terms of Use with you, discuss any questions you might have, and give you their permission to use the Communication Services with both your and their full understanding of these Terms of Use. Their consent is required for your use of any Communication Service. By using the Communication Services, you are telling us that you and your parent or guardian have joined in this agreement.
You agree to use the Communication Services only to post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and related to the particular Communication Service. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree that when using a Communication Service you will abide by the rules set forth below:
Use polite language. Objectionable or offensive language will not be tolerated at any time. You may not store, use or submit defamatory, hateful, libelous, obscene, vulgar, tortious, pornographic, sexist, racist, homophobic, inappropriate, unreasonable, violent, religiously-charged, threatening, abusive or illegal content, or content in violation of any third-party privacy or other rights.
Be courteous. You may not make threats or incite anyone else to violence or hatred. It is also prohibited to deliberately disturb any discussion with repetitive messages, unfounded messages or spamming.
Discuss but do not attack. In an open discussion where there are many different opinions, people often disagree. Knowledge encourages lively discussions and debates, however personal attacks are a breach of these Terms of Use.
You may not use the Communication Services to promote, advertise or offer for sale any good or service, to solicit funds, goods or services, to solicit other users to join or become members of any online or other services, to conduct or send any study, contest, pyramid scheme or chain letters, spamming, or to engage in any hacking, solicitation or any other act for illegal purposes. It is prohibited to use the Web Services or any Communication Service for autopromotion or to upload content for commercial purposes without Knowledge’s consent. Any communications which are harmful to minors are also prohibited.
You will not impersonate any person or entity, including, but not limited to, a Knowledge representative, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity.
You will not forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any submission transmitted through any Communication Service.
You will not submit or upload any virus, bug, malware or any other harmful computer code, program or file. You will not interfere with or disrupt the Communication Services.
You will not harvest or otherwise collect personal information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent.
You will not violate copyright or other intellectual property rights of others. Without limitation, you will not upload, post, email or otherwise transmit any material that infringes any patent, trade-mark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party.
You will not upload, post, email or otherwise transmit any material or information that you do not have a right to transmit under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under nondisclosure agreements).
You must comply with all applicable laws and regulations in your use of the Communication Services.
You must comply with any posted code of conduct, terms or other guidelines which may be applicable for any particular Communication Service.
Knowledge has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However, Knowledge reserves the right to review materials posted to a Communication Service and to remove any materials in its sole discretion. Knowledge reserves the right to terminate your access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time without notice for any reason whatsoever.
You should consider all communication through the Communication Services to be public and not private communications. Always use caution when giving out personally identifying information about yourself or your children in any Communication Service. Knowledge does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Communication Service and, therefore, Knowledge specifically disclaims any liability with regard to such user submitted content, messages or information, or otherwise with regard to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation in any Communication Service.
Knowledge reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in Knowledge’s sole discretion.
Your Submissions
You declare that you have all the necessary rights, in particular, intellectual property rights, to any material that you submit as a user of the Web Services to Knowledge through a Communication Service or otherwise.
You acknowledge and agree that you remain the holder of the copyright of all material you submit as a user to Knowledge. However, you acknowledge and agree that by submitting any materials or works to Knowledge, you grant it an irrevocable non-exclusive worldwide licence to use, edit, modify, delete, reproduce, publish, distribute, translate, develop ancillary products, adapt, communicate, perform in public, archive or index, and give sub-licences to such materials or works, or otherwise do any other act that is subject to copyright protection under the Copyright Act (Canada). You waive any moral right you may assert related to the integrity of your work. The rights granted in this section are applicable to all media, including without limitation all print media and digital or electronic media now known or hereafter created. The licences granted by you herein are perpetual and non-revocable.
No materials that you submit through a Communication Service will be subject to any obligation of confidence. No compensation will be paid with respect to any material that you submit to Knowledge as a user of the Web Services. Knowledge is under no obligation to post or use any such material you may provide and reserves the right, in its sole discretion, not to publish, to filter, to edit or to withdrawal any materials transmitted by a user, for any reason (or for no reason) whatsoever.
By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting materials to us, through a Communication Service or otherwise, you warrant and represent that: (i) you own or otherwise control all of the rights to such materials including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit such materials; (ii) such materials shall not violate the rights of any third party including, but not limited to, intellectual property and proprietary rights; and (iii) such materials shall not violate any law, statute, ordinance, regulation, or these Terms of Use.
You acknowledge and agree that you are personally liable for the content of your messages, articles or other content submitted on Knowledge’s Internet sites, and for the consequences thereof.
By using the Web Services you agree that Knowledge is not and may not be held liable for the accuracy, legality or the compliance with intellectual property laws or with the conditions of use of any materials provided by its users.
Limitation of Liability
To the fullest extent permitted by law, under no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall Knowledge be liable for any loss of use, loss of data, loss of opportunity, loss of income or profit, loss of or damage to property, or for any damages of any kind or character (including without limitation any compensatory, incidental, direct, indirect, special, punitive, or consequential damages), arising out of or in any way connected with the use of, or the delay in use or inability to use, the Web Services, contents of any Web Service, or any website or contents with which it is linked, even if Knowledge has been advised of the possibility of such damages or losses. If you are dissatisfied with any portion of the Web Services, or any of these Terms of Use, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Web Services. If Knowledge or any of its third party providers are found liable in any connection with a claim arising out of or related to using or accessing the Web Services, the aggregate liability to you for all damages, losses and causes of action, howsoever arising, shall not exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing the Web Services. This limitation of liability shall survive the termination of these Terms of Use.
You specifically acknowledge that Knowledge will not be liable for content or the defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any third party and that the risk of harm or damage from the foregoing rests entirely with you.
The Web Services are solely directed to individuals located in Canada. Knowledge makes no representation that any Web Service is appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who access or use the Web Services from other jurisdictions do so at their own volition and are responsible for compliance with local law.
Indemnity and Release
By using the Web Services you agree to indemnify Knowledge and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, volunteers and employees and hold them harmless from any and all loss, liability, damages, claims and expenses, including legal fees, arising from your violation of these Terms of Use, your use of the Web Services, or your breach or alleged breach of the copyright, trade-mark, proprietary or other rights of third parties. By accessing the Web Services you are agreeing to release Knowledge and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, volunteers and employees from any and all claims, demands, debts, obligations, damages (actual or consequential), costs and expenses of any kind or nature whatsoever, whether known or unknown, suspected or unsuspected, disclosed or undisclosed, that you may have against them arising out of or in any way related to your use of the Web Services or the products or services offered at or associated with the Web Services. You agree to waive all laws that may limit the efficacy of such release.
Termination and Modification
You agree that Knowledge, in its sole and absolute discretion, may terminate your password, account registration or use of any Web Services, and remove and discard any materials submitted by you through the Web Services, for any reason, including without limitation, if Knowledge believes that you have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of these Terms of Use. Knowledge reserves the right to remove any Content submitted by you to any Web Service without prior notice. Knowledge may also in its sole discretion and at any time discontinue providing the Web Services, or any part thereof, with or without notice. You agree that any termination of your access to the Web Services under any provision of these Terms of Use may be effected without prior notice, and acknowledge and agree that Knowledge may immediately de-activate or delete your account and all related information or other content in your account and/or bar any further access to such content or the Web Services. You agree that Knowledge shall not be liable to you or any third party for any termination of your access to any Web Service. The provisions of these Terms of Use pertaining to disclaimers, exclusion or damages, limitations of liability, indemnification and release shall survive termination.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
These Terms of Use, your use of the Web Services, and all related matters shall be governed solely by the laws of the Province of British Columbia, Canada and the applicable federal laws of Canada, without regard to the conflicts of law provisions of any jurisdiction. You hereby irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the Province of British Columbia in relation to all disputes arising from or related to these Terms of Use, your use of the Web Services and any related matters.
No Waiver
No failure or delay by Knowledge in exercising any right or privilege under these Terms of Use will operate as a waiver thereof, nor will any single or partial exercise of any right or privilege preclude any other or further exercise thereof or the exercise of any other right or privilege under these Terms of Use.
Severability
If any part of these Terms of Use are determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable laws, including but not limited to the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provisions will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of these Terms of Use shall continue in effect.
Entire Agreement
Unless specified herein, these Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between the user and Knowledge with respect to your use of the Web Services and the services offered at the Web Services, and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and Knowledge with respect to the Web Services.
Enurement
These Terms of Use are binding upon and shall enure to the benefit of the parties and their respective successors, heirs, executor, administrators, personal representatives and permitted assigns.
Compliance with Laws
Knowledge’s performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in these Terms of Use is in derogation of Knowledge’s right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the Web Services or information provided to or gathered by Knowledge with respect to such use.
Language of Contract
It is the express will of the parties that this agreement and all related documents have been drawn up in English. C’est la volonté expresse des parties que la présente convention ainsi que les documents qui s’y rattachent soient rédigés en anglais.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about the Web Services or these Terms of Use, please contact us using the following information:
Greater Vancouver: 604.431.3222Toll Free (Canada): 1.877.456.6988Fax: 604.431.3387
